Let's have a nice clean game.everyone.
Down.
Come on.move the puck.
Wendell! Move it! Move the puck!
Up here.Booth. Up here!
Back on D.
Pick 'em up.on D. pick 'em up.
Go.Booth! Go.Booth! Go.Booth!
Kill 'em.Booth!
What did he do that for?
It's what Booth does.
Keeps the other team honest.
He's what you call an enforcer.
What.like law enforcement?
Yeah.okay. Well.let's go with that.
Oh.what was that? What about the
cross-check? Ref.are you blind?
Pass it! I'm open! Pass it! I'm open!
Pick him off! Yeah!
That was a cheap shot.Carlson.
Yeah.you guys suck.
That's 24 Blue. two
minutes for charging.
For what?
- What about the cross-check
back there.huh? - Get in the box!
Come on.man. It's hockey.
Club hockey.and some of us have to
go work in the morning. all right.pal?
- Enough. Let's go.
- Carlson.clam down! Skate away.
- Just go in the box.
- Go on. get in there and sit down.
- Yeah.sit down.crybaby.
- Let's go.
Let's go.
So.this is punitive. right?
To be sent to this little area here?
Keep your head up next time.
number 12. Keep your head up.
Yeah.yeah.I'll be waiting.
Come on!
It's called a penalty
box. you know.send in.
Yeah.Booth committed a penalty when he checked
the big guy when he didn't have the puck.
Stay with him.Paul. Just stay with him.
There's a hit right there.Ref.
that you missed again.
Booth seems quite anxious to
get out of the disciplinary box.
Yeah.I've never seen
him this agitated before.
Open man! Open man!
- That's not good.right?
- No.
Go.Booth!
Wendell might get a basket!
Elbow.Ref! Elbow!
Is Wendell okay?
That can't be legal.
It definitely is not.
- Come on.Ref. you got to call
- Come on.what are you doing.Carlson?
Want to go?
Come on. come on. Let's
go. Come on.let's go.
Come on.Booth!
You're a dirty player.Carlson.
Come on.bro. Get your hands
free. Get your hands free.
You don't take shots at my
guys. You got that? Ends here.
Okay.Carlson?
Ends here.
Booth seems to be winning.
Well.it's Booth I'm worried about.
- That guy's out of control.
- No more.
I'm gonna have to call a
game misconduct on that one.
All right. You get up off the ice.we'll
finish this in the parking lot. Come on.
If you did your job.I wouldn't
have to do it for you. Look at him.
- He's hitting my guys.
- You all right.buddy?
Son of a bitch.
Get up. You all right?
Oh.did I score.man?
Oh.yeah. Yeah... Come on.
I do not know how I feel about this.
It's very primal.
I like it just a little too much.
- Come on.team.
- All right.come on.let's focus.
So.you still seeing double?
Only when I open more than one eye.
Your hand's busted.
Yeah.well.you know.
guy left his helmet on.
Hey.you two all right?
- What?
- Want to wait outside?
But your hand might be broken.
Do you want me to look at it?
No.it's all right. You
can wait outside please.
It's a men's locker room.Bones.
There comes a time in ice fishing when it's time
for the father to turn the drilling over to his son.
Man.this is a great day.
- You give me a beer. let me run the augur.
- Yup.
You're 18.Leo.
You start drilling
holes. it's safety first.
- You got me?
- Yeah.
Nothing I'm saying here
applies only to ice augurs.
You get me?
- All right.
- Good.
You know.that way. you don't fall through the
ice and die. or get a disease. or get pregnant.
- Dad.come on.
- Okay.
- Go ahead.
- All right.
That a boy. Keep her perpendicular.
Once you get it in a little bit.
you can speed her up.let her rip.
All right.let her rip.
Dad.she-she's bleeding.
- I... she's bleeding.
- Pull out. Pull out.
Oh.I hope that's fish.
You better go wait in the truck.
Hey.uh.what do you think there.Bones?
I would surmise that the body went into the
lake before it froze.then the lake froze.
then the body floated up and became
attached to the bottom of the ice.
I meant.was he murdered?
Um.maybe.
Could have been an accident
or a suicide.except...
- Oh.you shouldn't do that.
- It itches.okay?
Yeah.well.except for what?
Trauma to the left maxillary
orbit suggests violence.
It's kind of gross. what you're doing.
Gross? You got your finger
in some guy's maxillary orbit.
I don't think there's anything
else to be learned here.
so let's get this
Popsicle back to the lab.
Hey.look at that. Bones.you made a joke.
Well.I can be quite amusing.
Wait a second.
Booth.you aren't wearing any gloves.
Bones.I...
Remember that guy I punched out
last month during my hockey game?
- Pete Carlson?
- Yes. When you broke your hand.
That's him.
I'm a suspect. Here.
Bones Season04
Episode13 Fire in the Ice
Given that Agent Booth is currently
the prime suspect in this murder...
We don't know it's a murder.
Oh.look at that--
I'm the prime suspect.
Agent Payton Perotta here will
be working with Dr. Brennan.
I won't work the case without Booth.
In that case. I invite Agent
Booth's continued participation.
In the background as an advisor.
Agent Payton Perotta has earned bachelors
degrees in both forensic science and criminology.
Well.anything short of a doctorate
is virtually useless at my level.
How would you like to proceed.darling?
Well.it's pretty obvious. We definitely want
to interrogate the primary suspect.right?
Yeah.
Based on decomp. I'd put time of death
at about five days prior to freezing.
Local cops say the lake
froze over three weeks ago.
Aside from some dormant
anopheles mosquito larvae.
I imagine whatever the water from the lake
tells us. it'll be through a microscope.
If Booth is a suspect. then I should
be.too. This guy scrambled my brains.
Your alibi is that you were seeing double
and being taken care of by your mother.
I'll get on the fluid samples you
took from the lungs and esophagus.
Could be the vic was drowned somewhere
else and then dumped in the lake.
No. Drowning's not the way
Booth would kill someone.
Not that I actually
suspect Booth. At all.
Quit staring at me.
In the course of the game.the
victim and I exchanged blows.
Who initiated the fight?
It was hockey.
So.it was spontaneous combustion?
The guy hit two of my players.
The-The ref-- he didn't catch that.
And that made you angry?
Not angry enough.you know. to chase
him down after the game and kill him.
So.where did you go after the game?
Uh.Bones drove me and
Wendell to the hospital.
So.alibi that night or the next?
Bones and I are just partners.
Okay. Now you're answering questions
I had no intention of asking.
Is it your contention that.uh. your argument
with the victim was constrained to the ice?
That is my contention.
'Cause I have a-a witness who
stated you told Carlson. and I quote.
"You get up off that ice. and we'll
settle this out in the parking lot."
Trash talking.
Let me cut to the chase here.
- Did you kill Pete Carlson?
- No.
Did you dump his body in the lake?
No.I did not.Agent Perotta.
Do you feel that your experience as the child of an
abusive alcoholic has made you more prone to violence?
Excuse me.
What the hell are you doing?
It's part of my job to assist
the interrogating agent.
You know I didn't murder
anyone. Sweets.all right?
So what you're doing right
now is you're just studying me.
That's part of our agreement.too.
You have a question for
me. you ask me yourself.
Don't use her.
All right.okay.two questions.
One: am I picking up some sexual
tension between you and Agent Perotta?
How the hell do I know
what you're picking up?
Okay.Uh.two: underneath
your affable exterior
is a deep reservoir of rage.
My question is.do you always
have that under control?
You know.if I didn't. you'd be dead
right now instead of just wincing.
- I'm not wincing.
- Don't ever bring my old man up again.
Rats. I winced.
So...
Doyouhave any more questions? Thank you.
Yeah. You work out much?
Yeah.I'm pretty consistent.
You look like you take
excellent care of yourself.
Okay.this is useless.
Both patellas are fractured.
As though he'd fallen to his knees?
Yeah.with a great deal of force.
During a hockey game?
No.not if he wore pads.
I believe that this
is the cause of death.
Penetration of the lachrymal sac here.deep
into the inferior orbital fissure.
Yeah.I would have thought
a small caliber bullet.but...
- No sign of bullet fragments.
- Yeah.
This is Pete's apartment.
He wasn't the best housekeeper.
Ms. Withers.was Mr. Carlson
up to date on his rent?
Good question. Great start.
Uh.yes. Mostly.
500 bucks short.
He didn't need much. He
was a big kid at heart.
Poor Pete.
What he really loved was hockey.
I wouldn't be surprised if that's why
he joined the volunteer fire department.
I even got him this necklace.
Crossed hockey sticks.
You attended his games?
Oh.all of them. Yeah.
You were a couple?
It looks like someone went through all of his
belongings and then left them on the floor.
Oh.it always looked like that.
The car outside with the
flat tires.is that his?
Yeah.somebody slashed the tires
just before he disappeared.
Why didn't you report him missing?
I thought maybe.uh...
I thought he was staying
with someone else.
There's a lot of bills here.
"Final notice.past due..."
Looks like he couldn't afford
to feed his fish.either.
"Albie.Thursday.11:00 p.m."
Do you know who Albie is?
I don't know.
This is blood.
It's a hockey jersey.Bones.
You know.hockey players bleed
sometimes when they play the game.
Ms. Withers.how bad were
his financial problems?
Well.a couple days before Pete
disappeared. he asked me for $2.000.
Did he say what for?
He liked me. You know?
He was one of these guys.he...
he didn't say much. but
he could be real sweet.
And a man borrows money from a woman.
it means there's a bond of trust.right?
I don't understand your reasoning.
I do. It's definitely a bond of
trust. You're absolutely right.
We're terribly sorry for your loss.
Is that our victim?
Yes. The last of the tissue samples.
Wendell can clean the skeleton
now and you can do your thing.
You still think cause of death was
a projectile through the left eye?
Yes.but since we found no bullet.nor any
indication of gunpowder residue in the wound.
we're stumped as to
what kind of projectile.
The alveolus around the incisor is
cracked. the socket caked with blood.
This is a recent loss.
Well.he was a hockey player.
So basically. we're
talking about gladiators.
And I love it.
Perhaps the sight of males battling
stimulates the part of your brain
which has so far failed
to find a suitable mate.
And thank God you're here.
The water I found in the victim's
esophagus. not from the lake.
Lake water is microorganism infested.
Water in his
throat.deionized brine water.
He was killed. then dumped in
the ocean then dumped in the lake?
Deionized brine water freezes clear.
It contains an antifreezing agent.which
I know sounds counterintuitive...
Ice rinks.
Kind of jumped my
punch line there.Dr. B.
But.yes. We should see what
rinks are closest to the lake.
It's the one Booth played at.
I find it interesting that the
evidence keeps pointing toward Booth.
Pete Carlson was murdered?
Pete.he's indestructible.
Not so indestructible.
This guy took him down a few notches.
Made him stay down.too.
Well.it was the heat of the game.
All right.your guy crossed the line.
He was our enforcer.
Took the job real serious.
Well.whoever got Pete
must've got a drop on him.
Pete wouldn't go easy.
You mind my asking why
nobody reported him missing?
Well.the night after you flattened
Pete. we go up against the State Police.
Then Pete gets into a beef with
a big State Police left-winger.
'Cause you handed him his ass on a platter.
Pete maybe had something to prove that night.
You got a name?
Hey.Alex? Yo! Come here!
The fuzz player that Pete got into it with
his last game.do you remember his name?
Yeah.Lou Herrin. number five.
Pete took Herrin down with a real cheap shot.
He got tossed out the rest of the season.
Any chance that Pete and this guy.Herrin.
continued their fight off the ice?
People threaten.
Yeah.but nobody carries through.
Yeah.keep it on the ice.right?
If I were you.I would talk to Chloe.
- Who's Chloe?
- Chloe Bratton.
Chloe's a puck bunny.
Here and Pete put in some quality
mattress time before he dumped her.
Well.mattress really
isn't. uh.Chloe's style.
- No offense.
- None taken.
I favor backseats myself.
I can't believe Pete's gone.
How long ago did you two break up?
Break up? We didn't break up.
His teammates think you did.
No.we had this on-again/off-again
thing. It was casual. No biggie.
So you didn't mind that he
slept with different women?
I wouldn't have minded if he did.
but I happen to know he didn't.
Well.I happen to know
that he did. Right.
- Who?
- t doesn't matter.does it?
Given that your relationship
was so.um. casual?
You slashed his tires. didn't you?
- Agent Booth...
- No.
We can prove you did it. Chloe.so here's
the deal: you tell us the truth from now on.
and we won't charge you with vandalism
and obstruction of justice.okay?
- Let's try it again. You slashed...
- Agent Booth?
Yes. Of course.
Let's try this again.
You slashed his tires.didn't you?
Yes.
I mean.he was sleeping
with someone else.
I got passions that take over sometimes.
You know how it is when the guy you give
yourself to just goes off with someone else.
Who's.um.Albie?
Albie?
Albie runs this poker game in back
of a Chinese food joint off I Street.
Probably why Pete was
broke all the time.
So.who'd you say Pete was sleeping with?
I think we've got enough
information for today. Ms. Bratton.
Thank you very much
for your cooperation.
Thanks.
Any luck with the murder weapon?
Yes. We are certain it
is not a screwdriver.
Well.the blood on the victim's
jersey was all his own.
The rib cage has been bruised.
- It has?
- Yes.
See this vague pattern of bone bruising?
Yeah.it extends from the right clavicle
through anterior ribs four through eight.
He was struck repeatedly.
Like.by a hockey stick?
During the game maybe?
Not during. The.um.padding would
prevent that kind of bruising.
I'll take a closer look. I
can't believe I missed that.
No.I can't believe
you missed that.either.
I was signaling you to encourage Wendell
by saying anyone could've missed that.but...
You should have said so.
Booth says I stink at
nonverbal communication.
She said in the back.
Okay.well.just don't be pulling your
gun until you go through the kitchen.
or Mama-san there is going to
hit the panic button. Okay.just...
Ah.so you're ready to risk a gun fight
with your weapon in the wrong hand?
I don't have a wrong hand.
I'm curious.
When you shoot with your left hand. does
it feel like somebody else is shooting?
- What do we do now?
- Okay.FBI.
Okay.I'd reach for my badge
right now. but.you know...
Drop your weapons.please.
"Please"? The FBI does not say "please."
Okay.look. I really don't care
about the illegal gambling.
I just want to talk to a guy named
Albie about a guy named Pete Carlson.
I'm Albie.
First rule: don't kill the
people who owe you money.
All you get then is
trouble and no money.
How much money did Carlson owe you?
Okay.so you got your operation
shut down and moved out.
because I can have my guys here in about
what.three minutes to mop that back room up?
Pete Carlson was not a bad
player most of the time.but...
you know.every once in a while...
He got brave and lost everything.huh?
Gamble a bit yourself.do you?
I'm reformed.
Tell me.when was the last
time Carlson got.um.brave?
Last month.
But he paid up in full
a couple days later.
Cash?
Little garish. don't you think?
I don't know where Pete got
it. but it covered his debt.
I'm going to have to take this.
If I didn't intend to give it
to you. you'd never have seen it.
Okay.you gave me the time I needed to
move my operation. I gave you evidence.
I call us square.
You decide to get back into
the game. you look me up.
Right. Yeah.
Well.we gonna call this in?
Oh.no point. Like the
woman said.she's moved on.
Hodgins confirmed that the traces of
rink water in the victim's esophagus
came from this rink.
Well.how did rink ice
get into his throat?
He was beaten.then a sharp
instrument was thrust into his eye.
There should be blood stains.
You're going to scan the
ice with one little wand?
I'll call in an FBI forensics team.
We'll have the whole place searched.
No need. All you need
is black light.right?
- Yes.
- Right?
I got a great idea. just stay here.
It's very slippery. don't move.
Ready? How's that.huh?
- Nice.
- Gonna work?
Well.I see some.uh. flecks of blood.
No we're looking for something bigger
than these small specs and spots.
Uh.the victim was stabbed in the eye.
We're looking for a
pretty significant puddle.
Right.two guys get into a beef.then
they put their street clothes on
and then come back here on
the ice to duke it out? No.
- Booth?
- Yeah?
My God.
This is going to turn out to be
where Pete Carlson was murdered.
This is all the ice from the crime scene.
including the scrapings from the Zamboni.
We should be able to get enough DNA out
of this to confirm the blood is Carlson's.
Human tooth.
It's hockey. That Zamboni probably
had a hundred teeth in there.
Looks like we found where
the Tooth Fairy winters.
Did you find a match yet?
Just started.
Cam says it's definitely
the victim's blood.
I still haven't found the murder weapon.
Yeah.I know.I still haven't identified the
nylon polymer I found on the victim's shirt.
So.I've looked at.like. a thousand photos
of those blood patterns at the rink.
And tons from the apartment.
Why.what are you looking for?
Here's a blood pattern at the rink.
The body was dragged in that direction.
Yeah.the body was dragged that way.
but what are those drops over there?
What drops?
Those drops right there.
They parallel the dragging
body. And they aren't smeared.
These parallel drops
aren't from the victim.
They're from whoever
dragged him across the ice.
Well.that means we have to check
for more than just Pete's DNA.
Too bad we can't question the fish.
What killed those fish?
Not eating for three weeks.
If that happened. they
would eat each other.
Grab your coat. We're
going on a field trip.
And tell Cam to check the rink samples to
find out if there was a second source of DNA.
I'm not really a big fan of this...
barking out orders stuff.
Agent Booth. it's come to the
attention of the deputy director
that you are a viable
suspect in a murder case.
Right.okay.and he wants you to
make sure that I'm not viable.
That's correct.
Come on.Sweets. you know
I didn't kill anyone.
So.you know. put that in shrink talk and
write out your little form and send it in.
Mm-hmm.yes.of course. but to do that.
I need to ask you some questions.
Great. Shoot.
I saw you in that game.
You beat another man to the ice.
It's hockey. I was
protecting my teammate.
You broke your hand on his helmet.
It's hockey.
Okay.you never played.did you?
Oh.I'd run track and cross country
and did some wrestling and ch...
- Chess!
- No.
- Checkers?
- Didn't say that.
You know what? Then you know nothing...
It's about teams.okay? And teamwork.
Obviously you don't know
anything about that. Dr. Sweets.
You joined the army.
You became a sniper.
You joined the FBI.
Do you see the.uh. the binding
element in those choices?
It's violence.
Or the love of uniforms.
You ever think that?
Agent Booth. I believe that you
are ready to confront the fact that
the violence you may
have suffered in childhood
- You know what?
- has followed you into adulthood.
Fill out the form.
Not now!
Hiya.Sweets.
Uh.if you're about finished here.Booth. in
accordance with the warrant you made me get.
Pete Carlson's phone records are here.
Ms. Julian. actually.I'm the one
that decides when we're done here.
Of course you are.cherie.
no offense intended.
I'll be delivering the phone
records to Agent Perotta.
I thought I'd do that in your office.
Thanks.cherie.
We're done.
Well.we are done but that
was just a coincidence.
Sweets.I've killed but
I've never murdered before.
Look up the difference in your
little black book there.okay?
This is legal.right?
- Absolutely.
- Okay.
None of them look nibbled on.
Oh.man.they should've gone at each other like
a Peruvian soccer team stranded in the Andes.
Then they all died at the same time.
I don't see what this
is going to tell us.
How they died.
No.no.I mean about the case.
Ooh.if Brennan were here.
she'd smack your face.
Her philosophy is. we find out the facts about
everything. then see how it fits together.
Photo opportunity.
Pete made eight calls right
after the game to the same number.
Lou Herrin. Who's that?
A sergeant in the State Cops.
He exchanged blows with the
victim the night that he died.
Make it official. Question the cop.
Let's get some leverage
on the guy first.
Put him at the murder scene.
get a warrant to test his DNA.
Here we go.
Get a warrant for this.Ms.
Julian. get a warrant for that.
You need grounds for a warrant.cherie.
Don't they teach that
at Quantico anymore?
What grounds have you got for
that warrant? None! Nothing!
You're just wishing.
I know how to get some
blood out of this Herrin.
- Legally?
- Yeah.of course legally.
How?
Well.it's a big game tonight.right?
And sometimes during
a game... people bleed.
I don't like it.
Then you don't have to show up.
- What are you doing.man?
- What does it look like I'm doing?
You think that's a good idea? You got
another couple of weeks on that cast.
Well.considering I can't play with
a cast. then yeah.it's a great idea.
You clear about the plan?
Somebody bleeds. I collect a sample. put
it in a bag. pass it off to Dr. Brennan.
Lou Herrin.number five.
he's our prime suspect.
And I gotta make him bleed.
You've worked with Booth
for a while now.right?
Is he the kind of guy
that.uh. you know.I...
Is he flirty?
Flirty?
Would you say he twinkles
his eyes at all women?
Twinkly eyes actually result
when the pupils dilate very wide
which is an unconscious result of
intense interest or sexual attraction.
- So.no.he doesn't twinkle at everyone?
- No.
All right.
- Is that the guy?
- That's him.
Lou Herrin. number five.
You think he even knows how to bleed?
Just keep your head up.all right?
Come on. you should've called that.
Pass it up!
Keep your head up.Herrin.
Man.what's your problem?
I got a little chip.all right?
Just play your hockey.pal.
This guy's hard to get mad.
Man.he's maybe the only
one who hasn't shed a drop.
Stay out of my face!
Keep your head up.huh!
Take a warning.pal.
I think I'm finally getting to this guy.
Hope you survive it!
Taking a little break?
- Luc Robitaille?
- Seeley Booth.
Right.
Let's go.let's play.
You're the greatest
left-winger of all time.
And you're the best player on your team.
For what that's worth.
All right.let's go. Come on.let's play.
Here we go. Come on.show me something!
Hey.come on.move.move!
Move.move.let's go!
Whoa.wait a second. I can't play
hockey with you. I gotta solve a murder.
You know.Booth...
it's not about the blood.
It's our best forensic clue.
- Forget the blood.
- Then what?
You know what makes a
team. Look at the team.
It's about what brings a team together.
The team. Look at the team.
All right.let's go.one on one.
Let's see what you got. Come on.B.
Geez.ugh. I thought I could
get by you there.you know?
- You'll never get by me.
- Right.
Now.listen.Booth. you're
not your father.okay?
You protect the ones you care
about.on the ice and off the ice.
That's who you are.
You're not your father.
- Booth?
- You're not your father.
Booth?
Bones.what are you doing on the ice?
I get nervous when you
fall down and don't get up.
Come up here.
- Up you go.buddy.
- Come on.
Don't worry. I got the blood.
- Good work.Bones.
- But I'm Bones.
Smells like fish in here.
Yep. It's the victim's goldfish.
- They died of ammonia poisoning.
- How did that happen?
I don't know. Maybe the victim washed his
aquarium with window cleaner? I don't know.
How are things with you and Roxie?
Uh.good... good.
Taking it slow.you know.
Letting things unfold in a...
Are you seeing anybody?
I.um... actually went
out on a date last night.
I'm glad to hear that.
Any little twinge there?
Definitely a little twinge. yeah.but...
despite the twinge.I'm glad
you're back in the saddle.
Oh.I'm not back in the saddle
exactly. It was just a first date.
Barely got out of the barn.
You saw the victim's apartment.right?
Yes... yeah. Yeah.it was a pigsty.
I don't think that guy cleaned anything.
Not with ammonia. Not with anything.
I came as soon as I heard
Booth had a brain injury.
What part of your head hurts?
The part above my shoulders.
The doctor said he has a concussion.
He shouldn't fall asleep.
Otherwise. not serious.
Tell him about the hallucination.
You hallucinated?
Luc Robitaille gave me advice.
You got advice on a murder case from...
What did he say?
He said."Don't worry about
the... the player's blood."
That's very interesting.
Lucky Luc told me to look
in a different direction.
That's interesting.
Stop saying that... just stop.
Preliminary DNA tests show that the blood mixed
in with the victim's did not belong to Lou Herrin.
Lucky Luc was right.
All that means is that you got
your brains scrambled for nothing.
Lucky Luc is never wrong.
This hallucination could be.uh. Booth's
subconscious speaking to him through the voice
and image of someone that he idolizes.
Like a modern version of a Vision Quest?
You know what. hallucination or not...
Lucky Luc.he told me
something about myself that...
He told me something.
I'd be very interested
in knowing what he said.
Lucky for me.you're never gonna find out because
Bones is gonna drive me home and get me soup.
There has got to be some reason
these fish died of ammonia poison.
Last time I did this. I ended up
in juvie hall over the weekend.
- What?
Uh.nothing.
Buried treasure.
What do we do now?
Find out why the hell he was
hiding jewelry in a fish tank.
Have any of you ever heard of
something called "chain of evidence"?
Ms. Julian...
Why didn't you go with these
two idiots to the victim's home?
Please don't call my people idiots.
We're not idiots.
I feel like an idiot.
You don't speak right
now-- neither of you.
It's a crime scene.
My people are very often at
crime scenes. It's what we do.
No.it's not.
You've got it in your heads
that you're crime scene types.
This is Booth's fault for
indulging your fantasies.
You are not crime scene
types. You are lab rats.
No chain of evidence was broken.
When Dr. Hodgins and Mr. Bray found
the items. they immediately called me.
I called Booth. and when his head hurt too
much to talk to me. I called Agent Perotta.
- Ms. Julian...
- What?
A photograph of dead
fish led them to this.
I think that kind of
brilliance is worth it.
You've been taken hostage
by the squints.Agent Perotta.
Turns out these items were
reported destroyed in a fire.
The victim was a fireman.
The FBI could check to see if
the Firedawgs put out that fire.
Stole from the fire.
cleaned off with ammonia.
Hidden in the aquarium. killed the fish.
Okay. Now youarestraying
out of your territory.
No.they got it right.
The bracelet Agents Booth and Perotta
recovered from the victim's loan shark
was reported destroyed
by that same fire.
My people were right.
Your people?
We're Booth's people.
They're on the Firedawgs. but they also
played on the same high school team.
What brings them together.eh?
I'm back.
Hey.what brings them together?
What brings the team together?
So.I got the soup from the place.
And.yes.I told Mama that
it was for you especially.
It's all about the
team there. It's all...
- What are you doing?
- It's all about the team there.
Bones.it's all about
the team there. They...
these four guys...they all played
hockey together in high school.
and now they all play
together as a team.
- They're all firemen?
- Yeah. They all worked the jewelry store fire.
One of these three guys is the murderer.
According to Mr. Lucky?
It's Luc.okay? It is... it... it's
not Mr. Lucky. It is Luc Robitaille.
Left wing. Great shot.
Luc Robitaille-- he's one of
the best left wings of all time.
What is this?
It's a lace puller. Why?
I think it might be the murder weapon.
We want to discuss
the jewelry store fire.
- I want a lawyer.
- What for.Alex?
We didn't do anything
wrong. None of us did.
What about Pete?
He break some kind of fireman
code.something like that?
Yeah.something like that.
I've got nothing to say about
any of this. I want a lawyer.
We know Carlson was
beaten with a hockey stick.
after which a lace puller entered his
brain through his eye and killed him.
What about your dream.Ed?
You were gonna play for the NHL.right?
"Local player scouted by
the NHL." Look at that one.
Oh.this one's good.too.
"Fralic's hat trick wins game."
I got injured.
This injury would end any chance
of a career in professional hockey.
What does that have to do with anything?
Look.I got hurt. now I sell siding.
and I play hockey on the weekends.
Why you got to rub his face in the past?
Who ruined you?
Pete Carlson.
It was Pete.
You all knew about the stolen jewelry.
The question is.how many of you
were there the night he was killed?
None of us. Nobody here had
anything to do with that.
We have the hockey stick.
the murder weapon and DNA.
It's only a matter of time.
- Yeah.
- What?
It was me.
I asked to meet Pete on the
ice after everybody left.
I told him to give back the stolen
jewelry. and he said to me...
He said to me that I was a... a coward.
That I didn't do anything to him back
in the day when he wrecked my life
and I wouldn't do anything to him now.
Well.he was wrong.
I'm not positive this is a good idea.
Oh.I got you! I got you. Stay up here.
Okay.it's all right. Here we go. one more.
Well.you know what.I
got to stay up all night.
so who better to keep
me company than you?
You and me skating is saving
you from slipping into a coma?
Oh.easy.Bones. NowI'mgonna go down.
I have a lot of natural
athletic ability.
Oh.yeah.natural. I
can... I can see that.
Real smooth and natural.
That's it. Well done.
That Agent Perotta. she
really enjoyed working with us.
Yeah.
But.um...
you're the only FBI
agent I want to work with.
Will you tell me what the
Lucky Luciano told you?
He's not an Italian opera singer.
Bones.why do you always say that wrong?
- You do it on purpose. don't you?
- I would like to know what he said.
He said that I'm not like my old man.
He said I'm made of better stuff.
Well... I don't know your
old man. your father.but...
I think you're made of
very.very good stuff.
Hey.you know what? Forget
about Agent Perotta. all right?
Nothing's gonna change
between me and you.
Well.entropy is a natural force that pulls
everything apart at a subatomic level.
Everything changes.
- Not everything.Bones.
- Don't.
Not everything.
You're gonna make me fall.
I'm never gonna make you
fall. I'm always here.